Public Health Rounds UP246
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Public Health Rounds
1999 -- 2013
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
UP246
0.5 Linear Feet
6 Digital Object(s)
Arrangement
This collection is organized into one series.
Custodial History
Physical copies are received through intercampus mail while electronic copies are retrieved from the Public Health and Professional Degree Programs website: http://www.tufts.edu/med/news/newsletters/phpd.html.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains the semiannual Public Health Rounds newsletter published by the Office of Public Health & Professional Degree Programs. It reports on the activities of the programs, students, faculty, and alumni.
- Public Health Rounds, 1999 -- 2013; UP246.001; 0.5 Linear Feet; 6 Digital Object(s)
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains the semiannual Public Health Rounds newsletter published by the Office of Public Health & Professional Degree Programs. It reports on the activities of the programs, students, faculty, and alumni.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - GPPH Rounds, Fall, 1999; UP246.001.001.00001; Public Health and Professional Degree Programs (Box 1)
    Public Health
  - GPPH Rounds, Spring, 2000; UP246.001.001.00002; Public Health and Professional Degree Programs (Box 1)
  - GPPH Rounds, Fall, 2000; UP246.001.001.00003; Public Health and Professional Degree Programs (Box 1)
  - GPPH Rounds, Spring, 2001; UP246.001.001.00004; Public Health and Professional Degree Programs (Box 1)
  - GPPH Rounds, Fall, 2001; UP246.001.001.00005; Public Health and Professional Degree Programs (Box 1)
  - GPPH Rounds, Spring, 2002; UP246.001.001.00006; Public Health and Professional Degree Programs (Box 1)
  - GPPH Rounds, Fall, 2002; UP246.001.001.00007; Public Health and Professional Degree Programs (Box 1)
  - GPPH Rounds, Spring, 2003; UP246.001.001.00008; Public Health and Professional Degree Programs (Box 1)
    This issue is mis-labeled on the newsletter as Fall 2002 but it is actually Spring 2003.
  - GPPH Rounds, Fall, 2003; UP246.001.001.00009; Public Health and Professional Degree Programs (Box 1)
  - GPPH Rounds, Spring, 2004; UP246.001.001.00010; Public Health and Professional Degree Programs (Box 1)
  - GPPH Rounds, Fall, 2004; UP246.001.001.00011; Public Health and Professional Degree Programs (Box 1)
  - GPPH Rounds, Spring, 2005; UP246.001.001.00012; Public Health and Professional Degree Programs (Box 1)
  - GPPH Rounds, Fall, 2005; UP246.001.001.00013; Public Health and Professional Degree Programs (Box 1)
  - GPPH Rounds, Spring, 2006; UP246.001.001.00014; Public Health and Professional Degree Programs (Box 1)
  - Public Health Rounds, Fall, 2006; UP246.001.001.00015; Public Health and Professional Degree Programs (Box 1)
  - Public Health Rounds, Spring, 2007; UP246.001.001.00016; Public Health and Professional Degree Programs (Box 1)
  - Public Health Rounds, Fall, 2007; UP246.001.001.00017; Public Health and Professional Degree Programs (Box 1)
  - Public Health Rounds, Spring, 2008; UP246.001.001.00018; Public Health and Professional Degree Programs (Box 1)
  - Public Health Rounds, Fall, 2008; UP246.001.001.00019; Public Health and Professional Degree Programs (Box 1)
  - Public Health Rounds, Spring, 2009; UP246.001.001.00020; Public Health and Professional Degree Programs (Box 1)
  - Public Health Rounds, Fall, 2009; UP246.001.001.00021; Public Health and Professional Degree Programs (Box 1)
  - Public Health Rounds, Spring, 2010; UP246.001.001.00022; Public Health and Professional Degree Programs
  - Public Health Rounds, Fall, 2010; UP246.001.001.00023; Public Health and Professional Degree Programs (Box 1)
  - Public Health Rounds, Spring, 2011; UP246.001.001.00024; Public Health and Professional Degree Programs (Box 1)
  - Public Health Rounds, Fall, 2011; UP246.001.001.00025; Public Health and Professional Degree Programs (Box 1)
  - Public Health Rounds, Spring, 2012; UP246.001.001.00026; Public Health and Professional Degree Programs (Box 1)
  - Public Health Rounds, Spring, 2013; UP246.001.001.00027; Public Health and Professional Degree Programs (Box 1)
  - Public Health Rounds, Fall, 2013; UP246.001.001.00028; Public Health and Professional Degree Programs (Box 1)